Alex Soroka Minsk +375336389581 lehaSVV2009@gmail.com

Summary

5 years experience Full Stack Developer. Having fun with programming (backend or frontend, office or remote, paid or open source) and traveling. Trying to be useful in any team. Currently welcome to relocation offered jobs.

Skills

Java: 5 yearsJavaScript: 5 yearsSpring: 4 yearsReact JS: 3 years

Experience

Full Stack Developer, -, 12/2018 - 2/2019

Simple battleship-like board game.

- React
- Material UI
- Styled Components
- boardgame.io
- three.js
- brain.js

Full Stack Developer, Issoft Solutions, 5/2018 - 11/2018

React Question Board for meetings and planning using Interaxo document management system.

- REST API
- Spring
- Hibernate
- PostgreSQL
- React
- Material UI
- Redux
- React DnD
- React Virtualized

Frontend Lead Developer, -, 6/2018 - 9/2018

Web project with courses for students and teachers.

- React
- Redux
- Styled Components
- React Player
- Swagger

Backend Developer, Issoft Solutions, 2/2018 - 5/2018

Application allows to set up external workflow for different folders in document management system.

- REST API
- Spring
- Hibernate
- Apache Camel
- WebSocket

Frontend Developer, -, 3/2018 - 4/2018

Pinterest like room fittings.

- React
- Material UI
- Redux
- React Stack Grid

Frontend Developer, -, 11/2017 - 2/2018

Real estate search app.

- React
- Material UI
- Redux
- Leaflet

Backend Developer, Issoft Solutions, 1/2017 - 1/2018

REST Public API for big document management system.

- REST API
- Spring
- OpenID Connect
- OAuth2
- Keycloak
- Retrofit
- Swagger
- Docker
- Openshift

Backend Developer, Issoft Solutions, 7/2017 - 8/2017

Web and mobile applications for medical items monitoring on ships.

- Spring
- Hibernate
- Spock
- Swagger
- OAuth2
- Gradle
- MySQL
- Docker
- AWS EC2
- Bamboo

Full Stack Developer, Issoft Solutions, 10/2014 - 1/2017

Enterprise document management system for engineering and oil industry in Norway.

- Spring
- Alfresco
- CMIS
- JUnit
- Gradle
- ExtJS
- Cordova/Phonegap
- Google Analytics
- Jenkins
- Git

Java Developer, IBA, 8/2014 - 10/2014

Support of bank content management system.

• IBM Tivoli Storage Manager

Full Stack Developer, IBA, 2/2014 - 8/2014

Web based bank document management system.

- Apache Struts
- Dojo
- Ant
- IBM FileNet
- IBM WebSphere
- Apache POI
- SVN

Full Stack Developer, IBA, 9/2013 - 2/2014

Web based document management system.

- JSP
- Servlets
- XSLT
- Maven
- IBM FileNet
- IBM WebSphere
- Apache POI
- SVN

Education

BSUIR, 6/2016

Artificial intelligence

BSUIR, 6/2018

Ergonomics

Publications

• Al Knowledge base in cookery, BSUIR

Profiles

- Github, <u>lehaSVV2009</u>LinkedIn, <u>alex-soroka-74b070ba</u>
- Skype, <u>csi.alexsoroka</u>Instagram, <u>specialforkadet</u>